Rockwell Kent
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Alphabetical Files, circa 1900-1971, undated, Series 1:; (Reels 5153-5249, 5256, 5740-5741)
  - Hoggson, Donald, 1951 (Reel 5191, Frame 519-524)
  - Hoggson, Ella, 1952 (Reel 5191, Frame 525-529)
  - Henry Holt and Company, Inc., Publishers, 1947 (Reel 5191, Frame 530-533)
  - HoltenMoeller, Hugo, 1944-1945 (Reel 5191, Frame 534-538)
  - Hom-Gas Contract, 1950 (Reel 5191, Frame unfilmed)
    (utilities for Asgaard Farm)
  - Homar, Larry, 1962-1971 (Reel 5191, Frame 539-580)
  - Hoogstraten, W. N., undated (Reel 5191, Frame 581-584)
  - Hope, Bob, 1953 (Reel 5191, Frame 585-587)
  - Horace Mann School, 1911, 1950, 1961-1963 (Reel 5191, Frame 588-605)
  - Horley, F. V. (see: Faber & Faber, Ltd., Publishers) (Reel 5191)
  - Horses, 1940-1950 (Reel 5191, Frame unfilmed)
    (about purchase of horses, training, maintenance, and equipment)
  - Horton, H. Leavitt, 1948 (Reel 5191, Frame 606-609)
  - Horvath, Mr., undated, 1948, 1959 (Reel 5191, Frame 610-614)
  - Horwitt, Nathan George, 1927, 1950-1952, 1963-1968 (Reel 5191, Frame 615-678)
  - Hotel Bristol, 1945 (Reel 5191, Frame 679-685)
  - Hotel Drake, 1944 (Reel 5191, Frame 686-689)
  - Hotel Lexington, 1943-1948 (Reel 5191, Frame 690-708)
  - Hotel Piccadilly, 1947 (Reel 5191, Frame 709-711)
  - Hotel Vanderbilt, 1943 (Reel 5191, Frame 712-714)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1931-1936, 1966 (Reel 5191, Frame 715-749)
    (correspondence concerning book illustration)
  - The Hour Publishers, 1952 (Reel 5191, Frame 750-752)
  - Hourwich, Rebecca, 1928-1929 (Reel 5191, Frame 753-764)
    (correspondence about plans for Country Life article on Kent household)
  - House, 1939-1954 (Reel 5191, Frame 765-1561)
    (correspondence and invoices relating to routine maintenance, supplies, equipment, and improvements; also, warranties and printed matter concerning purchases)
  - House, cont. 1954 (Reel 5192, Frame 2-38)
  - House, Virginia Lou, 1939 (Reel 5192, Frame 39-42)
  - Housinau, Howard and Marie, 1955 (Reel 5192, Frame 43-46)
  - E. T. Howard Company (Art Reference Bureau), 1942-1943 (Reel 5192, Frame 47-102)
    (concerning commissions for illustrations and magazine covers)
  - Howard, Francis Nunan, 1966, 1969 (Reel 5192, Frame 103-129)
  - Howell, Ferdinand, 1919-1922 (Reel 5192, Frame 130-139)
  - Howell, Jack and Kay, 1956-1957 (Reel 5192, Frame 140-146)
  - Hoxsey, Dean C., 1960 (Reel 5192, Frame 148-149)
  - Hoxsey, Lowell and Ella, 1950-1961 (Reel 5192, Frame 150-161)
  - Huberman, Leo, 1950, 1953 (Reel 5192, Frame 162-166)
  - Hubert, Anne and Ed, 1964-1971 (Reel 5192, Frame 167-175)
  - Hudowalski, Grace, 1941-1945 (Reel 5192, Frame 176-198)
  - Hughes, Charles C., 1957-1961 (Reel 5192, Frame 199-243)
    (regarding purchase of a print; also, poem about Kent by Hughes)
  - Human Engineering Laboratory, 1947-1949 (Reel 5192, Frame 244-254)
  - William Hunrath Co., Inc., 1960 (Reel 5192, Frame 255-257)
  - Huntley, Victoria Hutson (see: Hutson, Victoria) (Reel 5192)
  - Hurd, Clem, 1949 (Reel 5192, Frame 258-260)
  - Hurd, Edith, undated (Reel 5192, Frame 261-264)
  - Hurok, Sol, undated (Reel 5192, Frame 265-267)
  - Hurst, Edna M., 1951 (Reel 5192, Frame 268-271)
  - Huson, Gordon, 1950 (Reel 5192, Frame 272-274)
  - Hutchins, Robert, 1955-1957 (Reel 5192, Frame 275-311)
    (includes correspondence about Kent's passport lawsuit)
  - Hutchins, Mrs., 1946 (Reel 5192, Frame 312-314)
    ([too dark to be legible])
  - Hutson [Huntley], Victoria, 1927-1933, 1947 (Reel 5192, Frame 315-357)
    (correspondence about Hutson's lecture on Kent, and letters of recommendation)
  - W. E. Hutton & Co., 1947-1950 (Reel 5192, Frame unfilmed)
    (statements, receipts, and orders to purchase and sell stock)
  - Hyde, Lawrence and Bettye, 1946, 1949-1952 (Reel 5192, Frame 358-584)
    (about publication and distribution of Southern Cross, Hyde's novel in woodcuts with an introduction by Kent; reviews)
  - H, Unidentified and Illegible, 1945-1969 (Reel 5256, Frame 14-25)
    (Faye, 1968-1969; Halfdan H., 1964; Jane M. H., 1957; Jessica Hei[?], 1945)
  - Iannelli, Alfonso, 1954 (Reel 5192, Frame 585-589)
  - Imported Publications & Products, 1959 (Reel 5192, Frame 590-592)
  - In Fact, 1942-1946 (Reel 5192, Frame 593-603)
  - Incorporation, 1919 (Reel 5192, Frame 604-645)
  - Independent Citizens' Committee of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, Inc., 1944-1946 (Reel 5192, Frame 646-683)
    (bylaws, meeting announcements, and invitations to speak)
  - Independent Voters' Committee of the Arts and Sciences for Roosevelt, 1944 (Reel 5192, Frame 684-690)
  - Indian Hill, 1951-1952 (Reel 5192, Frame 691-710)
    (correspondence about summer music camp planned by Mordecai Bauman)
  - Indonesian Veterans Group of the U.S. Armed Forces, 1946 (Reel 5192, Frame 711-715)
  - Information Bureau of the Soviet Union, 1941-1943, undated (Reel 5192, Frame 716-851)
    (correspondence concerning exhibition, speaking engagement, politics, Soviet-American friendship, fund raising for Russian war relief, news of mutual friends; miscellaneous printed matter; see also: Kon, Louis)
  - Information Please, 1945 (Reel 5192, Frame 852-856)
  - Inquiries, 1962-1970 (Reel 5192, Frame 857-905)
  - Institute for Cultural Exchange thru Photography, 1965, 1968 (Reel 5192, Frame 906-913)
  - Institute of American Sporting Art, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5192, Frame 914-916)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1942 (Reel 5192, Frame 917-927)
  - Institute of Soviet-American Relations, undated (Reel 5192, Frame 928-972)
  - Institution for the Chinese Blind, 1942 (Reel 5192, Frame 973-976)
    ([target incorrectly reads: Institute for the chinese Blind])
  - Insurance, 1941-1960 (Reel 5192, Frame unfilmed)
  - Inter-American Cultural Relations, 1941 (Reel 5192, Frame 977-980)
  - International Committee for Political Prisoners, 1942 (Reel 5192, Frame 981-983)
  - International Institute for Peace, 1958, 1961 (Reel 5192, Frame 984-1009)
    (mainly form letters)
  - International Institute of Arts and Letters, 1958-1960 (Reel 5192, Frame 1010-1017)
    (invitation to submit application; membership certificate)
  - International Labor Defense, 1937-1946 (Reel 5192, Frame 1018-1236)
    (inquiries about cover designs, invitations to serve on committee, correspondence about article by Kent for its newsletter; reports, minutes, and other printed matter)
  - The International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, 1943-1959 (Reel 5192, Frame 1237-1262)
  - International Lyceum Association, 1943 (Reel 5192, Frame 1263-1266)
  - International Mark Twain Society (see: Clemens, Cyril) (Reel 5192)
  - International Publishers, 1946, 1948, 1966 (Reel 5192, Frame 1267-1282)
  - International Rescue and Relief Committee, 1942 (Reel 5192, Frame 1283-1287)
  - International Student Service of the United States, 1941 (Reel 5192, Frame 1288-1291)
  - International Study Center, 1944 (Reel 5192, Frame 1292-1298)
  - International Workers Order, 1938-1955, 1960, undated (Reel 5192, Frame 1299-1528)
    (correspondence concerning Kent's lecture tours, appointments to committees, promotion of This Is My Own, layout and design of IWO publications, conference plans and arrangements, international politics, Kent prints donated for fund-raising purposes, benefit traveling exhibition, IWO's 50th anniversary celebration, activities of local lodges, legal actions by and against IWO, insurance benefits, N.Y. State Insurance Department's campaign to dissolve IWO, Policyholders' Protective Committee, artists' place in the labor movement; printed matter; see also: Culture; Milgrom, Sam; Tallentire, Molly; Tallentire, Norman; and Trauber, Jerry)
  - International Workers Order, cont. (Reel 5193, Frame 2-1558)
  - International Workers Order, cont. (Reel 5194, Frame 2-403)
  - Interviews, 1969, undated (Reel 5194, Frame 404-450)
    (transcript of Paul Cummings interview of Kent for the Archives of American Art; questions for Florence Lehmann interview of Kent; transcript of unidentified interview)
  - Introductions, 1917-1922 (Reel 5194, Frame 451-463)
  - Inverarity, Bruce, 1961-1971 (Reel 5194, Frame 464-677)
  - Investors League, Inc., 1946 (Reel 5194, Frame 678-685)
  - Invitation Lists (Reel 5194, Frame 686-726)
    (lists and letters of acceptance/regret for cocktail party honoring Aaron Douglas, January 1939; cocktail party for unveiling of Kent mural, April 1939; Farmers for Wallace picnic, summer 1943)
  - Irish Letters, 1926-1930, 1950, 1959-1966 (Reel 5194, Frame 727-887)
    (from friends in Ireland)
  - Irish Parcels Exporters & Importers, 1958 (Reel 5194, Frame 888-890)
  - Irwin, Rose (see also: Sweeties), 1950-1952 (Reel 5194, Frame 891-922)
  - Isaacs, Stanley M., 1941-1945 (Reel 5194, Frame 923-929)
  - It's Me, O Lord!, undated, 1957, 1969 (Reel 5194, Frame 930-934)
    (reviews and publicity; see also: Autobiography)
  - Ives, Burl, 1951 (Reel 5194, Frame 935-943)
  - Ivy College, undated, 1958 (Reel 5194, Frame 944-947)
  - Jackson, Ian, undated (Reel 5194, Frame 948-950)
  - Jackson, J. O., 1956 (Reel 5194, Frame 951-953)
  - Jackson, W. E., 1941 (Reel 5194, Frame 954-957)
  - Arthur Jaffe Heliochrome Company, 1953 (Reel 5194, Frame 958-961)
  - Jahn, Anna and Otto, undated (Reel 5194, Frame 962-964)
  - James, Alexander and Family, undated, 1938-1967 (Reel 5194, Frame 965-1376)
    (correspondence about Kent's writings, Danny's school problems and adventures in the merchant marine, Kent and James exhibitions, news of family and farming)
  - Jamieson, Margaret, 1956-1970 (Reel 5194, Frame 1377-1542)
    (fan letters, and correspondence about Kent's books, politics, social issues, peace movement, and McCarthyism)
  - Jamieson, Margaret, cont. (Reel 5195, Frame 2-224)
  - The Japanese-American Mirror, 1941 (Reel 5195, Frame 225-232)
  - Jay Taxpayers' Association (R.K., Chairman), undated (Reel 5195, Frame 233-235)
    (brochure)
  - Jefferson School, 1944-1947 (Reel 5195, Frame 236-250)
  - Jencks, Clinton and Virginia, 1955-1963 (Reel 5195, Frame 251-301)
    (correspondence about Clinton Jencks's case and appeal to Supreme Court; clippings)
  - Jenofsky, Abraham, 1950 (Reel 5195, Frame 302-307)
  - Georg Jensen, Inc., 1946, 1949 (Reel 5195, Frame 308-320)
    (about silver and jewelry design)
  - Jerome, V. J. (Jerry) and Alice, undated, 1965 (Reel 5195, Frame 321-454)
    (correspondence about politics, Browder case, antifascist youth magazine)
  - Jersey Creamline, Inc., 1945 (Reel 5195, Frame unfilmed)
    (concerning herd requirements for marketing dairy products under the Jersey Creamline trademark)
  - Jessup, Mrs. William, 1943 (Reel 5195, Frame 455-457)
  - Jewish Peoples Committee, 1941 (Reel 5195, Frame 458-471)
  - Jewish People's Fraternal Order, undated (Reel 5195, Frame 472-474)
  - The Jewish Survey, 1941-1942 (Reel 5195, Frame 475-519)
  - Jewish War Veterans, 1962 (Reel 5195, Frame 520-522)
  - Jobs, 1939-1952, 1963-1966 (Reel 5195, Frame 523-1518)
    (correspondence with clients; invoices, and miscellaneous printed matter concerning illustration, advertising work, trademarks, etc.; see also: Bookplate Clients; Device Clients; and clients by name)
  - Jobs, cont. (Reel 5196, Frame 2-286)
  - Jobs Not Completed, 1934-1953 (Reel 5196, Frame 287-391)
  - The Johnny Appleseed Bookshop, 1951 (Reel 5196, Frame 392-396)
  - Johnson, Albin E. (Jack), 1947-1969 (Reel 5196, Frame 397-449)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Arnold, 1955 (Reel 5196, Frame 450-452)
  - Johnson, Barbara (Mrs. J. Seward Johnson, Jr.), 1965-1970 (Reel 5196, Frame 453-488)
  - Johnson, Charlotte, 1958 (Reel 5196, Frame 489-496)
  - Johnson, Crockett, 1944 (Reel 5196, Frame 497-499)
  - Johnson, Dr., 1949 (Reel 5196, Frame 554-556)
  - Johnson, Oakley C., 1961 (Reel 5196, Frame 500-505)
  - Johnson O'Connor Research Foundation Incorporated and Human Engineering Laboratory, undated (Reel 5196, Frame 506-513)
  - S. C. Johnson & Son [Johnson's Wax] Stock Certificate (E. Willis Jones), 1938 (Reel 5196, Frame 514-549)
    (correspondence, invoice, and two drawings)
  - Johnson, William M., 1958-1959 (Reel 5196, Frame 550-553)
  - Johnstone, Shirley (see also: Kent, Sally), 1939-1940 (Reel 5196, Frame 557-633)
    (letter inquiring about secretarial position; letters from friends and relatives; target omitted)
  - Johnstone, Shirley (see also Kent, Sally), 1939-1940 (Reel 5740, Frame 10-33)
    (previously sealed correspondence with Kent regarding plans to travel to Plattsburg to assume her new position as his secretary, and personal letters)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1942 (Reel 5196, Frame 634-638)
  - Joint Committee to Defend WPA Workers, 1941-1942 (Reel 5196, Frame 639-663)
  - Jones, Caroline Merrick, 1947 (Reel 5196, Frame 664-667)
  - Jones, Dan Burne and Jacquie, 1941, 1949-1969 (Reel 5196, Frame 668-1534)
    (correspondence with Kent collector about: illustrated books and collecting, Jones's Kent bibliography, news of family and mutual friends, purchase of paintings and prints, decoration of Jones's home with Kent fabrics, discussion of Rockwell Kent Foundation, reviews of It's Me, O Lord, politics, opinions of Catholic Church)
  - Jones, Dan Burne and Jacquie, cont. (Reel 5197, Frame 3-868)
  - Jones, E. Willis (see: S. C. Johnson & Son and Jones, Ruth and E.Willis) (Reel 5197)
  - Jones, J. A., 1926 (Reel 5197, Frame 869-872)
  - Jones, John, undated (Reel 5197, Frame 873-876)
  - Jones, Louis C., 1963 (Reel 5197, Frame 877-879)
  - Jones, Louise Seymour, 1943, 1946 (Reel 5197, Frame 880-885)
  - Jones, Mrs. Newton, 1941 (Reel 5197, Frame 886-889)
  - Jones, Ruth and E. Willis, 1957, 1960 (Reel 5197, Frame 890-893)
  - Josefsson, Mr. and Mrs. Johannes, 1948 (Reel 5197, Frame 894-896)
  - Josephson, Neil D., 1956-1960 (Reel 5197, Frame 897-932)
    (correspondence about polar explorations and Kent's Greenland stamp)
  - Josephy, Robert, 1941 (Reel 5197, Frame 933-935)
  - Joslin, Peter, undated (Reel 5197, Frame 936-941)
  - Joyce, Elaine and Martin, 1955 (Reel 5197, Frame 942-949)
  - Peter A. Juley & Son, 1938-1955 (Reel 5197, Frame 950-958)
  - The Junior League of the City of New York, Inc., 1942, 1944 (Reel 5197, Frame 959-967)
  - Junior Philatelic Americans, 1963, 1965 (Reel 5197, Frame 968-971)
  - Jury Duty, Essex Co., N.Y., 1946 (Reel 5197, Frame 972-978)
  - Justamon, Monique, 1950 (Reel 5197, Frame 979-993)
  - Justice Department, 1958 (Reel 5197, Frame 994-996)
    (books, politics, social issues, peace movement, and McCarthyism)
  - Kahn, Albert E. and Rietta, 1948-1961 (Reel 5197, Frame 997-1539)
    (correspondence about: World Congress for Peace, national and international politics, Kahn's writings and passport case, International Workers Order insurance problems, peace movement, news of problems, peace movement, news of family and friends, Rietta's "Mistone" garden sculpture business, trips to the USSR, and Kent gift of paintings to Friendship House; manuscripts of Kahn articles; clippings)
  - Kahn, Albert E. and Rietta, cont. (Reel 5198, Frame 3-1042)
  - Kahn, Arthur, 1950 (Reel 5198, Frame 1043-1047)
  - Kahn, Edith (Mrs. Mortiz Kahn), 1962-1970 (Reel 5198, Frame 1048-1073)
  - Kaplow, Alicia, 1966 (Reel 5198, Frame 1074-1076)
  - Kapp, Herman W., 1962-1966 (Reel 5198, Frame 1077-1119)
  - Kappa Pi Honorary Fraternity, 1942 (Reel 5198, Frame 1120-1125)
  - Kapustin, Razel, 1941 (Reel 5198, Frame 1126-1128)
  - Katcher, Stanley A., 1942 (Reel 5198, Frame 1129-1134)
  - Kautt, Alfhid, 1969-1970 (Reel 5198, Frame 1135-1151)
  - Kayden, Eugene M., 1950-1970 (Reel 5198, Frame 1152-1207)
  - Kazay, John J., 1965 (Reel 5198, Frame 1208-1210)
  - Keenan, Lawrence, 1952 (Reel 5198, Frame 1211-1213)
  - Keene Valley Hospital, 1963 (Reel 5198, Frame 1214-1216)
  - Keep America out of War Congress, 1941 (Reel 5198, Frame 1217-1220)
  - Keeseville Bakery, 1946 (Reel 5198, Frame 1221-1223)
  - Keller, Charles, 1949-1965 (Reel 5198, Frame 1224-1258)
    (correspondence about Keller's work, and family news; invitations to exhibitions)
  - Kellogg, Ray S., 1954 (Reel 5198, Frame 1259-1262)
  - Kelly, Gerald, undated (Reel 5198, Frame 1263-1266)
  - Kelly, Tim, 1945 (Reel 5198, Frame 1267-1271)
  - Kelsey, Leroy C., 1940-1941 (Reel 5198, Frame 1272-1275)
  - Kelsey, Mary, 1906, 1947-1948 (Reel 5198, Frame 1276-1327)
    (Easter postcard; correspondence regarding purchase of house on Monhegan Island, Maine)
  - Kelsey, R., 1915 (Reel 5198, Frame 1328-1331)
  - Kenerdine, Blanche, 1941 (Reel 5198, Frame 1332-1336)
  - Kennedy, Anne Reid, 1962-1965 (Reel 5198, Frame 1337-1346)
  - Kennedy, Jocelyn Pierson [cousin], 1970 (Reel 5198, Frame 1347-1351)
  - Kent, H. J., 1944 (Reel 5205, Frame 1095-1097)
  - Kent, Norman, 1942-1947, 1965 (Reel 5205, Frame 1098-1115)
  - Percy Kent Bag Co., Inc., 1945 (Reel 5205, Frame 1116-1121)
  - Kent, Richard T., 1970 (Reel 5205, Frame 1122-1125)
  - Kent, Sherman, 1967 (Reel 5205, Frame 1126-1131)
  - Kent Collection, 1953-1947, 1960-1961 (Reel 5199, Frame 117-323)
    (transcript of VOKS Section of Fine Arts (Moscow) opinions of Kent's paintings, checklist with prices; letters of appreciation and commendation from Soviet citizens and officials for Kent exhibition and gift of paintings; see also: Gift Correspondence; and Friendship House)
  - Kent Family (Reel 5198)
    - Kent, Barbara [daughter], 1919-1930 (Reel 5198, Frame 1353-1381)
      (correspondence with parents and brother; see also: Carter, Barbara Kent and Alan)
    - Kent, Clara [daughter], 1918-1951, undated (Reel 5198, Frame 1382-1528)
      (correspondence about school, employment, etc.; see also: Pearce, Cap and Clara Kent)
    - Kent, Clara [daughter], cont. (Reel 5199, Frame 3-116)
    - Kent, Dorothy [sister], 1919, 1946-1970 (Reel 5199, Frame 324-534)
      (family news)
    - Kent, Douglas [brother], 1947-1952 (Reel 5199, Frame 535-567)
      (about financial matters and health)
    - Kent, Frances [second wife], 1926-1943, undated (Reel 5199, Frame 568-1557)
      (mainly love letters, some of which are illustrated; also, correspondence about family and travels; a few letters from friends and mother-in-law; notebook with Eskimo translations; see also: Gay, Frances and Grisha; Frances Higgins vs. William Higgins; and Lee Family)
    - Kent, Frances [second wife], cont. 1926-1943, undated (Reel 5200, Frame 3-567)
    - Kent, Frances [second wife] (see also: Gay, Frances and Grisha), 1926-1948, undated (Reel 5740, Frame 34-789)
      (previously sealed love letters and letters about daily events written to Rockwell while he was on lecture tours, during Frances's extended visits to Arizona, and after their divorce; some are illustrated)
    - Kent, Frances (Mrs. Percy Kent) [aunt], 1913, 1943-1948 (Reel 5200, Frame 568-587)
      (correspondence about Kent genealogy, Kent painting she owns, and reminiscences of times when Rockwell and Kathleen lived in her house)
    - Kent, Gordon [son], Phyllis [wife], and Trini [ex-wife], 1928-1971, undated (Reel 5200, Frame 588-1552)
      (childhood memorabilia, including drawings, homework papers, and grade cards, with correspondence about academic work, social activities, and finances; correspondence about Gordon's service in Arctic unit of U.S. Army Air Force during World War II, medal awarded for heroism, an dproblems with commission; correspondence about graduate studies in physics, teaching, political activities in Progressive Party, divorce and remarriage; correspondence with Trini, Gordon's first wife, concerning her medical problems and employment; news of family and friends)
    - Kent, Gordon [son], Phyllis [wife], and Trini [ex-wife], cont. (Reel 5201, Frame 3-537)
    - Kent, Kathleen W. [first wife], 1907-1971, undated (Reel 5201, Frame 538-1569)
      (letters of congratulations from relatives and friends on engagement and marriage; correspondence with husband, mainly love letters, with reports of daily activities and news of relatives, some illustrated; marital problems, family news, Kent's painting progress and employment as a draftsman and in advertising; trips to Alaska, Newfoundland, and South America; divorce and finances; see also: Divorce Data)
    - Kent, Kathleen W. [first wife], cont. (Reel 5202, Frame 3-1573)
    - Kent, Kathleen W. [first wife], cont. (Reel 5203, Frame 3-917)
    - Kent, Kathleen [daughter], 1918-1935, undated (Reel 5203, Frame 918-1242)
      (correspondence with parents, including childhood drawings and samples of schoolwork, about: school, finances, housing and employment in New York City, and family news; see also: Finney, Kathleen Kent and Peter; Mannes, David and Marya)
    - Kent, Natasha (Tasha) [granddaughter], 1961-1969 (Reel 5203, Frame 1243-1572)
      (correspondence about her desire to study in the USSR, and inquiries on her behalf; arrangements for Tasha to study in England)
    - Kent, Natasha (Tasha) [granddaughter], cont. (Reel 5204, Frame 3-20)
    - Kent, Richard (Dick) [stepson] and Claire, 1929-1967, undated (Reel 5204, Frame 21-181)
      (correspondence about school, with homework papers and drawings, family news, and about Dick's experiences in the army and marital problems)
    - Kent, Rockwell, III [son], 1914-1971 (Reel 5204, Frame 182-1283)
      (correspondence with parents, including letters from boyhood bicycle trip between Connecticut and Cuba, about: school, finances, farm failure and debts to father, remarriage and family news; a few letters from his children; see also: Overton, Walter)
    - Kent, Sally (Shirley Johnstone) [third wife], 1940-1941, 1959-1960 (Reel 5204, Frame 1284-1564)
      (legal papers and correspondence concerning U.S. citizenship; correspondence with Johnstone family; see also: Family; and Johnstone, Shirley)
    - Kent, Sally (Shirley Johnstone) [third wife], cont. (Reel 5205, Frame 3-268)
    - Kent, Sally (Shirley Johnstone, third wife; see also Johnstone, Shirley), 1941-1967, undated (Reel 5740, Frame 790-1248)
      (previously sealed correspondence with Rockwell includes love letters, news of business and personal activities)
    - Kent, Sally (Shirley Johnstone, third wife; see also Johnstone, Shirley), continued, 1941-1967, undated (Reel 5741, Frame 12-43)
    - Kent, Sarah Holgate [mother], 1908-1947, undated (Reel 5205, Frame 269-939)
      (correspondence about family, friends, and financial matters, with letters from Anne Avery (companion) reporting on health; letters of condolence upon the death of Sarah H. Kent; see also: Avery, Anne)
    - Kent, Sarah Holgate, Estate of (see also: United States Trust Company of New York), 1953 (Reel 5205, Frame 940-997)
    - Kent, Susan [granddaughter], 1942, 1951-1959, 1969 (Reel 5205, Frame 998-1066)
      (correspondence, mainly concerning repayment of a loan)
    - Kent, unidentified, 1912-1947, undated (Reel 5205, Frame 1067-1094)
      (letters from unidentified relatives, mainly children; also, genealogical notes)
  - Keppel, David (Harlow, Keppel & Co., Inc.), 1941-1943 (Reel 5205, Frame 1132-1209)
    (correspondence concerning prints consigned for sale; see also: Harlow, Keppel & Co., Inc.)
  - Kerlan, Dr. Irvin, 1949 (Reel 5205, Frame 1210-1213)
  - Kerr, Howard M., 1945 (Reel 5205, Frame 1214-1217)
  - Ketchum, MacLeoud & Grove, Inc., 1948 (Reel 5205, Frame 1218-1229)
  - Keyser, Sherwood, undated (Reel 5205, Frame 1230-1232)
  - Keyser, Susan, 1970 (Reel 5205, Frame 1233-1247)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita, 1962 (Reel 5205, Frame 1248-1251)
  - John G. Kidd & Son, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5205, Frame 1252-1258)
  - Kilburn, Clarence E., 1944 (Reel 5205, Frame 1259-1272)
    (letters to Kilburn and newspaper editors about the congressman's voting record)
  - King, Dr. Harold G., 1948 (Reel 5205, Frame 1273-1279)
  - King, Mertie Johnson, undated (Reel 5205, Frame 1280-1282)
  - King, Sally (Mrs. Tom C. King), 1958 (Reel 5205, Frame 1283-1285)
  - Kingman, Dong, 1942-1945 (Reel 5205, Frame 1286-1293)